(Stuart:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)Turns out,
they guard the iPods,
(Leonard:)but they don't
guard the shirts.
(Howard:)So, how'd it go?
(Leonard:)It was going well.
(Leonard:)I was showing
this super hot girl
(Leonard:)how to boot up in Safe Mode.
(Leonard:)The manager got suspicious,
and, well, long story short,
(Leonard:)they really do have
a little jail in the mall.
(Howard:)Just FYI, don't try to go
back with a fake mustache.
(Howard:)I mean, they may not
really be geniuses,
(Howard:)but they see
right through that.
(Leonard:)I want to invoke
the girlfriend pact, Howard.
(Howard:)You that desperate?
(Leonard:)No, I just...
I want what you have.
(Leonard:)You know, I want
a woman in my life.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Holy Moses,
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)how much liquid can
be in one tokus?
(Leonard:)To be clear, I meant like
Bernadette, not your mother.
(Howard:)Yeah, I know
what you mean.
(Leonard:)Well, I'm off to meet
Bernadette's friend.
(Leonard:)How do I look?